<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Eco</string>
    <string name="action_go">Write Lyrics</string>
    <string name="lyrics_generator">Lyrics Generator</string>
    <string name="label_prompt">Prompt</string>
    <string name="prompt_placeholder">
        Imagine you are a songwriter looking at this image. It sparks a strong feeling and a story in your mind.
        Write full song lyrics inspired by this image.  Aim for a complete song structure, including verses, a chorus, and potentially a bridge, if appropriate.
        As you write, think like a songwriter capturing inspiration from a scene:
        Identify the dominant emotion or feeling conveyed by the image. Is it about love, memories, time passing, commitment, celebration, or something else?
        Extract visual details and elements from the image. Think about the setting, objects, text, and overall composition. Use these visual elements as imagery and metaphors in your lyrics.
        Develop a narrative or story suggested by the image. Who are the people involved (if any are implied)? What is the occasion or context? What story can you tell through song lyrics?
        Structure your lyrics into a song format. Aim for: At least two verses to develop the story or theme.
        A recurring chorus that captures the central emotion or message. Optionally, a bridge to provide a change in perspective or emotion, or to build towards a conclusion.
        An outro or final lines to bring the song to a close. Let the image guide your songwriting process.  Create lyrics for a full song that evokes the mood and tells a story inspired by what you see.
    </string>
    <string name="image1_description">Cupcake</string>
    <string name="image2_description">Cookies</string>
    <string name="image3_description">Cake</string>
    <string name="image_description">Image %1$d</string>
    <string name="results_placeholder">(Results will appear here)</string>
    <string name="gallery_screen">Memories</string>
</resources>